In this exercise, there are two questions that
you guys may find difficult.
They are question three and question five.
Let's look at question three.
The first distractor here is a contradiction.
Listen to these sentences from the audio.
In fact, being generally active is much better
for you than doing a lot of intense
exercise once in a while.
As you know, that can put as much strain
on your body as doing nothing at
all.
Here the speaker says that a certain kind
of exercise can put strain on your body.
This directly contradicts the idea in option A,
which is it protects the body from strain.
Because the information is the opposite of what
is stated, we can cross out option A.
In the audio, the speaker said.
As long as you're active for about an
hour a day, you'll find that you don't
stay up at night stressing about a project,
and that's a key benefit of staying active.
You can see that a key benefit is
a direct paraphrase of particularly important benefit.
The challenge here is to connect the signposting
phrase, a key benefit, back to the information
that came just before it, which is stressing
about a project.
Now for question five, this question tests your
ability to identify the main point of a suggestion.
Not just the keywords you hear, this is
a very common type of question.
In the audio, you will hear this sentence.
There are recycling bins provided, so please use
them.
If you only focus on the keywords, you
might quickly choose option C, use recycling bins
for all their waste.
However, this is a distractor.
The instruction to use the bins is a
smaller, secondary part of a larger point.
David says, Please make sure you don't leave
empty food containers or used mugs lying around
in the kitchenettes.
Therefore, B is the main point and the
correct answer.
The distractor in question five is hearing the
exact words, recycling bins, and choosing that option
without considering the wider context of the speaker's
main message.
Next, you will practice these skills in another
exercise of multiple choice questions with single answer.
See you soon!